<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Explore ByteBurst Smartphones Area for cutting-edge consumer electronics, latest smartphone innovations, reviews, and tech trends. Stay ahead with ByteBurst!"Explore iOS and Android operating systems, the leading software powering consumer electronics, from smartphones to tablets. Discover their features and differences."Explore the latest advancements in camera technology within consumer electronics. Discover innovations enhancing photography, videography, and everyday digital imaging."Explore the latest advancements in display technologies transforming consumer electronics, from OLEDs to 8K resolutions, enhancing visual experiences."Explore cutting-edge battery life and charging innovations revolutionizing consumer electronics, enhancing efficiency, sustainability, and user experience."Ensure data safety with top mobile security solutions in consumer electronics. Protect your devices from threats and enhance privacy effortlessly."Discover the latest in wearable devices: smartwatches, fitness trackers, and more. Stay connected and monitor health effortlessly with cutting-edge consumer electronics.Discover the latest in consumer electronics with smartwatches—your ultimate tech companion for fitness, notifications, and connectivity on the go."Discover the latest fitness trackers in consumer electronics, blending health monitoring with smart technology for an active lifestyle.""Discover the future of consumer electronics with Augmented Reality Glasses, blending digital and real worlds for an immersive experience like never before!"Explore cutting-edge health monitoring devices in consumer electronics for real-time fitness tracking, vital signs monitoring, and enhanced wellness management."Wearable Payment Solutions: Revolutionizing consumer electronics with seamless, secure, and convenient payment methods integrated into everyday wearable devices."Discover the latest in home entertainment systems, from smart TVs to surround sound, elevating your consumer electronics experience to new heights."Discover the latest Smart TVs in consumer electronics, offering advanced features, streaming apps, and seamless connectivity for an enhanced viewing experience."Explore top streaming devices and services in consumer electronics for seamless entertainment with the latest features, quality content, and user-friendly interfaces."Discover top soundbars and home theater systems for immersive audio experiences. Elevate your entertainment with cutting-edge consumer electronics.""Discover the latest gaming consoles in consumer electronics, blending cutting-edge technology with immersive entertainment for gamers of all ages.""Explore immersive experiences with Virtual Reality Headsets, the cutting-edge innovation in consumer electronics for gaming, entertainment, and beyond.""Explore personal computing devices in consumer electronics: laptops, tablets, and smartphones enhancing productivity and entertainment seamlessly."Explore the latest in consumer electronics with our top picks of laptops and ultrabooks, offering cutting-edge performance and sleek designs for all your tech needs.Discover the latest tablets in consumer electronics—portable, versatile devices perfect for work, entertainment, and everything in between.Explore the latest desktop computers in consumer electronics for powerful performance, advanced features, and cutting-edge technology. Ideal for work, gaming, and more!Discover the latest trends in consumer electronics, from cutting-edge gadgets to smart home devices, all designed to enhance your digital lifestyle."Discover versatile convertibles in consumer electronics: devices that seamlessly transform from laptops to tablets, offering flexibility and convenience.""Explore top computer peripherals like keyboards and mice in the consumer electronics market for enhanced productivity and gaming experience.""Discover must-read insights on the latest consumer electronics, featuring top reviews, trends, and buying guides to keep you ahead in tech.""Explore Smart Home Technology in Consumer Electronics: Enhance convenience, security, and energy efficiency with the latest connected devices for modern living."Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home revolutionize consumer electronics with hands-free control, smart home integration, and personalized user experiences."Smart lighting enhances homes with customizable, energy-efficient lighting solutions controlled via apps or voice assistants. A key innovation in consumer electronics.""Explore top security cameras and doorbells in consumer electronics. Enhance home safety with smart, reliable surveillance solutions. Shop now for peace of mind!"Discover advanced thermostats in consumer electronics, enhancing comfort and energy efficiency with smart controls and seamless connectivity."Discover the best home automation hubs in consumer electronics to control smart devices effortlessly and enhance your home's efficiency and convenience."">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://tech.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/49e89749e897.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #913664!important;

}
.w3c1a2504ff6ae10775676b0fed1a57e3 p,.w3c1a2504ff6ae10775676b0fed1a57e3 span,.w3c1a2504ff6ae10775676b0fed1a57e3 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.cc6ebe8bce41b7697229a73853a6cbb4e{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 14.7px 30.4px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.bf4d40e3b9f6a81b61da1337c794b6b3f p,.bf4d40e3b9f6a81b61da1337c794b6b3f a,.bf4d40e3b9f6a81b61da1337c794b6b3f span,.bf4d40e3b9f6a81b61da1337c794b6b3f label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.bf4d40e3b9f6a81b61da1337c794b6b3f a,.w3c1a2504ff6ae10775676b0fed1a57e3 a{
color:#070707!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.w3c1a2504ff6ae10775676b0fed1a57e3 a{
font-size:16px;
}
footer{
background:#080808;
color:#ffffff;
}
.yf60650c5cb6bc83ce4e97e8c36afff49:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50px 50.5px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:7.8px;
padding-right:7.5px;
padding-top:5.1px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.5px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://tech.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/49e89749e897.jpg" src="img/49e89749e897.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="navbar-nav d-flex align-items-center ml-auto"><li class="nav-item"><a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 nav-link" href="https://tech.netlify.app/news.html"  >News</a></li>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 nav-link" href="https://tech.netlify.app/index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">ByteBurst Smartphones Area</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/index.html"  >ByteBurst Smartphones Area</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/operating-systems-ios-android.html"  >Operating Systems iOS Android</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/camera-technology.html"  >Camera Technology</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/display-technologies.html"  >Display Technologies</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/battery-life-and-charging-innovations.html"  >Battery Life and Charging Innovations</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/mobile-security.html"  >Mobile Security</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73" href="https://tech.netlify.app/wearable-devices.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Wearable Devices</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/wearable-devices.html"  >Wearable Devices</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/smartwatches.html"  >Smartwatches</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/fitness-trackers.html"  >Fitness Trackers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/augmented-reality-glasses.html"  >Augmented Reality Glasses</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/health-monitoring-devices.html"  >Health Monitoring Devices</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/wearable-payment-solutions.html"  >Wearable Payment Solutions</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 nav-link" href="https://tech.netlify.app/home-entertainment-systems.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Home Entertainment Systems</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/home-entertainment-systems.html"  >Home Entertainment Systems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/smart-tvs.html"  >Smart TVs</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/streaming-devices-and-services.html"  >Streaming Devices and Services</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/soundbars-and-home-theater-systems.html"  >Soundbars and Home Theater Systems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/gaming-consoles.html"  >Gaming Consoles</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/virtual-reality-headsets.html"  >Virtual Reality Headsets</a>
  
<li class="dropdown nav-item ">
<a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="https://tech.netlify.app/personal-computing-devices.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Personal Computing Devices</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/personal-computing-devices.html"  >Personal Computing Devices</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/laptops-and-ultrabooks.html"  >Laptops and Ultrabooks</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/tablets.html"  >Tablets</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/desktop-computers.html"  >Desktop Computers</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/in.html"  >in</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/convertibles.html"  >Convertibles</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/computer-peripherals-keyboards-mice.html"  >Computer Peripherals Keyboards Mice</a>
  
<li class=" dropdown nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 nav-link" href="https://tech.netlify.app/must-read.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Must Read</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/must-read.html"  >Must Read</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/smart-home-technology.html"  >Smart Home Technology</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/voice-assistants-eg-amazon-echo-google-home.html"  >Voice Assistants eg Amazon Echo Google Home</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/smart-lighting.html"  >Smart Lighting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/security-cameras-and-doorbells.html"  >Security Cameras and Doorbells</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/thermostats.html"  >Thermostats</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://tech.netlify.app/home-automation-hubs.html"  >Home Automation Hubs</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="https://tech.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Smith Pro Outlet</h1>
<p>At Smith Pro Outlet one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Smith Pro Outlet and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Smith Pro Outlet. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Smith Pro Outlet, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Smith Pro Outlet follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Smith Pro Outlet.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Smith Pro Outlet, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Smith Pro Outlet has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Smith Pro Outlet's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Smith Pro Outlet does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Smith Pro Outlet</br>
822-179-8242</br>
7988 Main Street</br>
Santa Ana, CA, 92701</br>
USA</br>
</br>
<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="d19da4b2b0a290a3a591b6bcb0b8bdffb2bebc">[email&#160;protected]</a></br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 pt-5 container" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73" href="https://tech.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73" href="https://tech.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="y9e7872c088ed63231e9962aa6ed13c73" href="https://tech.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
<p><p>The content provided on this blog is for informational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. The information presented here is not meant to substitute professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this blog.</p>

<p>The authors and administrators of this blog are not healthcare professionals, and viewing this content does not create a doctor-patient relationship. We do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, relevance, or timeliness of any information on this site and are not responsible for any errors or omissions in this information nor for the availability of this information.</p></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script data-cfasync="false" src="/cdn-cgi/scripts/5c5dd728/cloudflare-static/email-decode.min.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
